<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[1048]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsshoptab]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shop Pro for THE Social Network]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Products on Facebook & Social Networks]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Set up a "Shop" tab on your Facebook page and increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website. Boost your Facebook community]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/1048-shop-pro-for-the-social-network.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1048.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Set up a "Shop" tab on your Facebook page and increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website. Boost your Facebook community.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2011 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  Show your products directly on the social network. Effective way to boost your sales, enjoy the power of your Facebook community to communicate about your shop and increase the number of visitors and orders on your PrestaShop store.  LEVERAGE THE POWER OF YOUR FACEBOOK CUMMUNITY TO GENERATE TRAFFIC AND SALES ON YOUR SHOP Increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website and boost your Facebook community. It’s a real way to grow your sales: take advantage of your Facebook community to communicate and bring your audience to your shop. This module is compatible with the multishop feature.Shop Pro for THE Social Network&nbsp;is also compatible with most shared SSL certificates (certified to work with OVH shared SSL hosting) The module also lets integrate statistics tracking via Google Analytics to measure its performance A live built-in preview of the module will help you set it up, and you can then easily link it to your Facebook page in a single click. "Shop Pro for THE Social Network" will help you improve your brand image and reach.  INCREASE THE NUMBER OF « LIKES » ON YOUR PRODUCTS AND THEIR VISIBILITY For each product, a "Like" button is included, which will allow visitors to share and talk about your products. Clicks on"Like" buttons will have impact on your website’s SEO and its position in Google search results. We also offer you to go even further : use your Google Analytics code to get your statistics as to the effectiveness of your Facebook Shop.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.1.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[69.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/835133-pprod/shop-pro-for-the-social-network.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/835133-pbig/shop-pro-for-the-social-network.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2072]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedtopmenu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu - Responsive]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Menu]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Discover and choose the most popular and more powerful responsive mega menu for PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/menu/2072-advanced-top-menu-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2072.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Discover and choose the most popular and more powerful responsive mega menu for PrestaShop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu allows you to build all types of horizontal navigation bars: single bar, drop-down menus, rich menu, mega-menu with columns.  Advanced Top Menu is a PrestaShop Addon that will help you to simplify the navigation and usability of your website. Give to your visitors an overwiew of your catalog making them to quickly find the desired product.  Thanks to its highly modular design, you will be able to use your menu bar to display images, promotions or advertisements, and put forward your offers and services that make your store unique.  With a rich configuration interface, it makes you able to customize your menu bar without special technical knowledge:ResponsiveUnlimited number of tabsUnlimited number of columnsUnlimited number of elementsSimple and complete graphical customizationAutomatic menu generation from your catalogAll content types supported: categories, manufacturers, suppliers, CMS, custom links...Conditional display depending on the status of your visitorNew version 1.10  A faster and cleaner configuration interface New default theme for optimal design out of the box New appearance settings New specific settings for mobile A Sticky mode, which let your menu always visible regardless of scroller position Allows you to restrict the display of some elements for desktop or mobile view Allows you to add different images for each language Opening animation effect on submenus Delay on opening submenus Contextual help tips in Back Office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.12.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573526-pprod/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573526-pbig/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fast & Mass Update]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/fast-mass-updates/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add to this category and add them in one click! You also can control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2889]]></id><name><![CDATA[blockyoutubevideos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Videos - YouTube]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Videos & Music]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bring your product pages to life&nbsp;on your site and make them interactive by adding videos!  The Product Videos - YouTube module is an ideal way to increase your products&rsquo; conversion rate]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/videos-music/2889-youtube-instant-suggest.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2889.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bring your product pages to life&nbsp;on your site and make them interactive by adding videos!  The Product Videos - YouTube module is an ideal way to increase your products&rsquo; conversion rate. It lets you easily and automatically import your YouTube videos and add them wherever you like on your product pages.&nbsp;  &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Videos are an essential tool to make your products more attractive and improve your conversion rate. 73% of consumers are more likely to purchase a product or a service after they&#39;ve watched a video.   This module is an essential tool for your site and your customers: &nbsp;Make your products more attractive by providing your customers with visual and relevant complementary information (features, characteristics, benefits, use, etc.).&nbsp;Increase your conversion rate and reduce product returns. 96% of consumers think it&#39;s easier to reach a decision about an online purchase if they watch a video.&nbsp;Easily enrich your site&#39;s content and improve your natural SEO by adding YouTube videos to your product pages.&nbsp;Improve customer engagement and increase average cart size on your site.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625269-pprod/youtube-instant-suggest.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625269-pbig/youtube-instant-suggest.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanagerforprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Modules]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently!&nbsp;*** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***&nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/modules-prestashop/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently!&nbsp;*** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you.Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!&nbsp;Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management.Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!&nbsp;Spend an Hour, Save a Day!Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds.For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you.&nbsp;Take Your Online Business to the BankBuy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules.Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/572842-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/572842-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (natural Search Engine Optimization)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a better place on Google.  To optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an internal linking that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[164.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[129.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analytics & Statistics]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/analytics-statistics/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop's and products' profitability !  The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly, profit and profit margin.  Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like "what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?".  This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.    You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.10.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[164.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[129.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/767436-pprod/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/767436-pbig/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5711]]></id><name><![CDATA[zipcodezone]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipping fees based on zipcodes]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Costs]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-costs/5711-shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5711.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With PrestaShop, it is possible to apply different shipping fees based on country or state. However, this does not necessarily represent the reality of carriers. Some will charge higher prices for mountainous or remote areas for example (departments or overseas territories). Improve your shop's shipping system with this module which will allow you to apply different shipping fees based on zip code of your client. Using the zone system of PrestaShop, you will be able to cut a country into as many parts as you want. By department, area or whatever you want. This has the advantage of adapting the way you want your areas. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/650424-pprod/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650424-pbig/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6144]]></id><name><![CDATA[gsnippetsreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (natural Search Engine Optimization)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful customer rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6144.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful customer rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With Google Rich Snippets, benefit from visually enhanced results on Google's search engine results and increase your click rate, numbers visitors and sales ! The full rating and review system will also greatly improve your shop's conversion rate and further increase your sales.  If you have already purchased our Facebook PS Wall Posts module (sold separately on http://addons.prestashop.com/en/social-commerce-facebook-prestashop-modules/4429-Facebook-PS-Wall-Posts.html), you can have any rating / review automatically posted on your Facebook fan page.  This module is also fully compatible and integrates with Presta-Module's "Advanced Pack 5" module, available on http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 & 2014 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.  You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/761381-pprod/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/761381-pbig/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6337]]></id><name><![CDATA[codfee]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cash On Delivery With Fee/Surcharge Plus (COD)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Collect On Delivery (COD)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/collect-on-delivery-cod/6337-cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6337.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method. More than 5,000 downloads and highly rated!The favourite payment method for your customers!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ESSENTIAL MODULE! This module will increase your sales! You can offset the extra cost of this shipping method by charging a fee to the customer. The cash on delivery payment method allows your customers to pay for the order at the time of receiving their order, they pay on shipment. This payment method is the perfect solution for customers who do not trust other payment methods, such as a card payment or PayPal, and prefer to pay upon receiving their order. With this method, you can offset the additional cost normally associated with "cash on delivery" by charging a fee to customers that choose this payment method. This module allows you to add the "cash on delivery" payment method with the option of applying an extra fee. Compatible with back office orders! Customers will benefit from the payment options most used and preferred by them. This module DOES NOT require a monthly fee or any other fee, you buy it once and you use it without any restrictions. Our guarantees ✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote. Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812425-pprod/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812425-pbig/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Assign your features as you want]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Search & Filters]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/search-filters/6356-multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add features to your PrestaShop catalog without limits!  With Multiple Features, you can assign as many values as necessary for the same product and the same feature. Remove this PrestaShop limitation and start using your features as you want!  If you also use our layered navigation system Advanced Search 4 (Winner of PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), you can give to your customers a more relevant research in your catalog.  Customer study :  Ocarat.com: "Some jewelry may have a different composition and an alloy of several metals. PrestaShop provides the ability to associate a feature to a product. However, I want to integrate in my shop a gold ring set with diamonds and emeralds. But features tab does not allow me to do so. I can't assign multiple values to a single purpose. So I have to choose between gold, diamonds or emeralds. Multiple Features remove PrestaShop limits and allows you to use features as you want !"]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6946]]></id><name><![CDATA[invoicepayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Invoice Payment ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Payment by Invoice]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The Invoice Payment is the most favorite payment method among German users and also very popular worldwide]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/payment-invoice/6946-invoice-payment.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6946.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The Invoice Payment is the most favorite payment method among German users and also very popular worldwide. With this module, you can offer the invoice payment method to your registered customers in order to provide a safe shopping experience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With this module, you can offer a bill payment to your users. You can define from what order this payment method is available for your customers. For example, for your regular customers this method should be available from their 2nd order. You also can define the order amount limit this method is available to. Further, you can set the payment terms, that depend on the selected order status. After the status has changed, the payment term also appears in the PDF invoice. In the module's configuration you also have a text area for further information. For example, you can specify where the customer should transfer the money to. This information appears in the PDF invoice]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[25.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/689390-pprod/invoice-payment.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689390-pbig/invoice-payment.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price Increment/Reduction by group, category and more]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Promotions & Gifts]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With our module you can set the product prices to your customers which do you want to really have]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/promotions-gifts/7422-price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With our module you can set the product prices to your customers which do you want to really have. Increments, reductions (discounts) and massive fixed price changes with an unlimited conditions and combinations to modify your product prices.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Change the product prices massivelyYou can change the price of the products massively, setting an increment, a discount or a fixed price using these conditions:- Category- Product- Customer group- Customer- Country- Zone- Supplier- Manufacturer- Language- Currency If you choose the percentage type, it can be calculated from Retail or Wholesale price and with or without taxes.To apply the rule, you have this additional controls: - Minimum threshold price- Maximum threshold price- Date From- Date To And also, you can control the final price result setting a minimum and a maximum price with: - Minimum result price- Maximum result price The module adds a priority system in case that two or more rules must be applied to the same product. In this case, you can establish a priority to set the order and if you want to only execute one of this rules (using the option:"Apply only one condition").  Discounts managementTo apply and manage the discounts with our module, you have 3 options: - Show reduction as discount: With this option enabled, the reduction is showed like discount (specific price), then the price of the product will show the old price and the new price with the discount amount/percentage.* Only works if the rule configuration create with our module is a discount. - Skip other discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will not be applied to this product.- Override discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will be applied and the previous discount will be overrided (ommitted but not deleted).This 2 options, are applicable with any of the configurations that you can do with our module. Examples of using the module:- Very useful for the promotions season like Black Friday, Sales, Christmas, Cyber Monday, etc... to change the prices in the products with begin and end date activating and deactivating the offer automatically.- You can set an increment in the catalog products only or a currency (or currencies) to avoid the currency conversion losses.- Set a reduction for a VIP customers group offering them more competitives prices or set an increment to your Resellers group to get more benefits from the products.- Change the prices in a Country or Zone and promote the sales in this geographical area. * The module doesn't change the original price of the product (you never will lose the original price). ★ ¡New! ★ -> Attributes filter (combinations)With the new attributes filter you can set the price changes only for an specific product combination.Example: Modify the price only of your product with the L and XL size and not for the prices of the S and M size. ★ ¡New! ★ -> Features filterWith the new features filter you can set the price changes only for products with an specific feature.Example: Modify the price only for the cotton and synthetic products. ★ ¡New! ★ -> Quantity product units filterAdded a new field to set the mínimum quantity units of the product that must be in the cart to apply the change in the price.Example: Modify the price of product from 3 units, then, the price of product will be changed automatically only if 3 or more products are added to the cart. ★ ¡New! ★ -> Change the prices within a period (date from and date to)Configure the price changes (increment, discount or fixed price) between 2 dates, or from a date or until a date. It's an optional field, is not necessary to set a date, if 0 there's no period limit to apply the rule.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20 until 2016-10-30Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) until 2016-10-30.  ★ ¡New! ★ -> Threshold prices to apply the rulesApply the change in your prices only for the product which price is between a threshold.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 10€ and less than 30€.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 50€.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is less than 100€.  ★ ¡New! ★ -> Minimum and maximum result priceNow, you can set a minimum and a maximum price to get if the result of the increment or discount is below or above this prices.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 200If the result price after the rule application is below 100€ (89€ for example), the product price will be 100€. If the result price after the rule application is above 200€ (205€ for example) the product price will be 200€.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 0If the result price after the rule application is below 100€ (89€ for example), the product price will be 100€. If the result price after the rule application is 105€ the product price will be 105€.Example: Minimum result price = 0 and Maximum result price 100If the result price after the rule application is above 100€ (105€ for example) the product price will be 100€. If the result price after the rule application is 80€ the product price will be 80€.  ★ ¡New! ★ -> Category tree to select the categoriesNew friendly interface in the Categories selector. Now, the display is in a category tree to select the categories easily.  ★ ¡New! ★ -> Friendly multiple selectors interfaceNew friendly multiple selector interface with add and remove buttons and a search box.  Geolocation compatibilityFull compatibility with Prestashop Geolocation to change the prices by Zone and Country. If the customer is not logged and the Prestashop Geolocation is enabled, the prices will be shown by the geolocation IP Country of the customer.If logged, the country and the zone calculation is done from the address delivery.  Apply a markup or offer a discount in your productsFeel free to play with a markup in the price of your products creating an increment or a reduction configuration by category, by product, by customer group, by customer, by country, by zone, by supplier and by manufacturer. Example: You can create a new category, associate the products to this category and with our module you could set all this category products to 20$ without changing the original product price and without creating complicated discount rules to obtain the desired price.  No multistore needed for the same catalog productsThe customers group filter allows to avoid creating a multistore for a B2B and B2C store, sharing the same catalog products but with different prices in each.  Our guarantees ✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote. Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812413-pprod/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812413-pbig/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7484]]></id><name><![CDATA[newsletterpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Newsletter & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/newsletter-sms/7484-newsletter-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7484.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that advertising plays a key role in promoting any business. Using our newsletter will boost your sales faster and easier than any other newsletter module available on the market. This module is an easy and fast way to send customizable newsletters about top selling products or special offers to your clients.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[69.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/724699-pprod/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724699-pbig/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8204]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsconnect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Connect for Social Networks, Amazon and Paypal]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Social Login & Connect]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Let your customers easily register and log in to your shop via Facebook, PayPal Login, Amazon, Google and /or Twitter]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/social-login-connect/8204-connect-for-social-networks-amazon-and-paypal.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8204.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Let your customers easily register and log in to your shop via Facebook, PayPal Login, Amazon, Google and /or Twitter.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your shop's conversion rate and sales by making registration and login as easy and frictionless as possible.  DISCOVER OUR OTHER COMPLEMENTARY FACEBOOK MODULES​&nbsp;Social Plugins: "F", Google, Pinterest, Twitter… : https://addons.prestashop.com/en/share-buttons-comments/5025-social-plugins-f-google-pinterest-twitter.htmlShop Pro for THE Social Network :&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/1048-shop-pro-for-the-social-network.html&nbsp;Fan Coupon for THE Social Network :&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/social-rewards-coupons/8130-fan-coupon-for-the-social-network.html  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the&nbsp;2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support&nbsp;: when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/835082-pprod/connect-for-social-networks-amazon-and-paypal.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/835082-pbig/connect-for-social-networks-amazon-and-paypal.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Legal]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/legal/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.  Complete compliance with the law  Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."  Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.  Main features of the modulesDisplay a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consentDisable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.Fully customize the warning banner (color, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency, buttons...) Getting the user consent   The module includes 2 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled. We recommend you to use this mode, this one allows you to fully comply with the law.Acceptance through the navigation: If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)  Customizing the banner content and design  As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).  The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, color, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background color of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is multilingual and automatically detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.  Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots crawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.  Disabling the modules that use cookies  This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookies on their computer with their consent.  "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law  To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.  Multistore mode  The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[25.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pprod/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pbig/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8741]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmulistecommandes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Improved Order List]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Order Management]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/order-management/8741-dmu-improved-order-list.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8741.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The more orders you have to process, the more this module will save you time. As much by the fact that all information is available from the order list and because you will be able to change status in mass with this module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/740079-pprod/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/740079-pbig/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8895]]></id><name><![CDATA[freedeliverymanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Free Delivery Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Shipping Costs]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/shipping-costs/8895-free-delivery-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8895.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction. According to the rules you have chosen, you encourage customers to increase the value of their purchases in order to take advantage of free delivery.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Developing your sales by increasing the value of transactions has never been an easy thing to implement. The &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module is actually the perfect solution for offering your respected customers free shipping through objective rules. It is the promise of a rise in the amount of orders with total control of delivery costs.  The module allows you to calculate in advance, with the help of precise rules, the necessary conditions for unlocking free delivery. The management and monitoring are done according to carriers, delivery area, price, weight, or any other criteria you term as important for your business.  The &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module offers control of delivery costs by releasing delivery available as a function of criteria you have chosen. All the carriers have their own price list. You may, for example, indicate a minimum order amount by carrier In presenting to the customer, in their order summary, the amount remaining before delivery is available, so you definitely encourage them to order more.  Highly detailed statistics visually present two types of reports together. The first one presents the number of orders that have benefited from free delivery, as well as the total and per-order amount that this cost you. You really control the impact of delivery costs. The second report displays the detail of costs caused by free postage and the orders where the rules for free shipping are applied. Thus, the &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module increases the value of transactions as well as the number of orders!  This module has been constantly evolving, many thanks to user feedback. TimActive, in fact, grants great importance to your perception of our solutions and of the improvements that can be added.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/691962-pprod/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691962-pbig/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart (Upselling)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cross-selling & Product Bundles]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/cross-selling-product-bundles/11345-push-on-cart-upselling.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Easily increase your average cart value by offering customized discounts to your client in the shopping cart summary !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Push on Cart module:Easily increase your customer&rsquo;s average cart valueClear unsold products from your inventoryGet your customers to discover new products to create a need and even secure their loyaltyCreate demand for new productsCapitalize on impulse purchasesImprove customer satisfaction and loyalty with customized discounts on select products Push on cart User Reviews:&nbsp; Comment&nbsp;posted on 2015-06-27&nbsp; &quot;Your addon helped bring in over a thousand dollars in extra sales. When I updated my website version and design, the module was turned off for a while. I&#39;m glad it&#39;s back on again. Thanks again!&quot; M. Pak  Comment&nbsp;posted on 2014-08-29 21:55:04 &quot;Good module, maybe could be usefull to have a random product offer&quot;&nbsp;J. S&aacute;nchez*  Comment&nbsp;posted on 2014-03-18 07:31:35 ​&quot;Good!&quot;&nbsp;T. Aarestrup  * Feature added to the module !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/push-on-cart-upselling.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/push-on-cart-upselling.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[RockPOS Point of Sale (POS) Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Point of Sale (POS)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Thanks to RockPOS (formerly Point of Sale Pro), now you can sell your products online and offline as well, at your stores / warehouses, exhibitions, trade conferences or via phone / chat]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/point-of-sale-pos/13654-rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Thanks to RockPOS (formerly Point of Sale Pro), now you can sell your products online and offline as well, at your stores / warehouses, exhibitions, trade conferences or via phone / chat. All transactions are connected to your cloud database.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sell your products anywhere, anytime in secondsCentralize your data, no need extra time to combine your manual orders]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[164.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[129.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/618511-pprod/rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/618511-pbig/rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[cartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Abandoned Cart Reminder Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Shopping Cart Abandonment]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/16535-abandoned-cart-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[An automatic email is sent to customers each time they add products to their shopping cart but do not purchase. It reminds and encourages them to complete the order. It&rsquo;s beneficial and easy to use!&nbsp;Automatically send one or more personalized emails to remind your customers about the contents of their cart. This helps turn abandoned carts into sales.Easily create email templates tailored to match your online store&rsquo;s theme.Also, you can now propose discounts directly via the email in order to remind your clients to finalize their purchases.&nbsp;  Abandoned Cart reminder Pro allows to easily add discounts on a product price or free shipping cost directly on the email depending on each clients cart amount.&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.23]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[134.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[94.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595057-pprod/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595057-pbig/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18656]]></id><name><![CDATA[jmarketplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[JA Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplace Creation]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplace-creation/18656-ja-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18656.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Best module of Spain in PrestaShop Awards 2015.  This module allows you to integrate several shops in the same economic platform and common retail space. All members can benefit from the sales force other vendors to obtain greater visibility increasing the number of customers and sales.  This integration of sale is currently one of the most effective ways to compete with traditional large surfaces and large ecommerce operators (Amazon, eBay, etc.).  With this module you can join in their market strength of different suppliers to have more visibility and more sales.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.7.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[214.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[169.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/717058-pprod/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/717058-pbig/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18921]]></id><name><![CDATA[mailchimp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mailchimp Newsletter & Statistics - 1.6 & 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Newsletter & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Manage your newsletters easily with this module allowing you to create, send and monitor customized newsletter campaigns from the PrestaShop back office]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/newsletter-sms/18921-mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18921.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Manage your newsletters easily with this module allowing you to create, send and monitor customized newsletter campaigns from the PrestaShop back office.  Thanks to Mailchimp,&nbsp;send up to 12,000 e-mails a month for free !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With official Mailchimp for PrestaShop, you can:Create entirely personalised newsletters.Add product images to your newsletters in 1 clic and schedule them easily.Promote customer loyalty by importing your Mailchimp customer lists and updating your customers with your special offers and latest news of your store.Update your customer lists at any time with the new ones registered with your store.Maximise reading and opening rates thanks to customer segmentation (mailings to customers who have opened or clicked on a previous newsletter, etc.).Monitor your campaigns using full reports and statistics included directly in your PrestaShop back office.Benefit from the Mailchimp free plan which allows you to send 12,000 emails per month and have 2,000 suscribers for free ! &nbsp; Mailchimp is already used by more than 7 million customers, now it is your turn!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[144.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[99.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pprod/mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pbig/mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19584]]></id><name><![CDATA[tacartreminder]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Smart Cart Reminder]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Shopping Cart Abandonment]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/19584-smart-cart-reminder.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19584.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it. The advanced solution for the abandoned cart reminder is what will fit your reminder emails, your promotions to your customers&#39; cart.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[According to the abandoned cart content, and information about the customers, the Smart Cart Reminder module is the advanced solution that allows you to remind your abandoned carts in an autonomous and focused way.  &laquo;&nbsp;The only module of the cart reminder without subscription offering as many features&nbsp;&raquo; &nbsp;** EMAILS OF REMINDER AND OFFERS ABOUT MARKETING ADAPTED TO EACH CART ** Indeed, the module allows you to create &quot;Reminder rules&quot; according to:Customer information (country, age, gender, group, etc.)Cart contents (amount, products, product categories, stock remaining, etc.)Time of year (Christmas, New Year&rsquo;s, Valentine&rsquo;s Day, Mothers&rsquo; Day, etc.) &laquo;&nbsp;No more untimely and inappropriate promotions which let you feel that you are desperate !&nbsp;&raquo;  With the reminder rules, create easily your own algorithms, for example:  Rule 1&nbsp;: For the cart that exceeds $90, which still contain available items in my stock, the customer is in USA. Then create a discount coupon to obtain the shipping costs for free. Reminder1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Free shipping costs&nbsp;&raquo; email. Reminder2: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only a few days to benefit from the offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 2: For the new customers, create a 5% Off Your Order. Reminder1: 1H after the dropped cart: send the &laquo;To celebrate your arrival 5% Off Your First Order &raquo; email. Reminder2: 24H after Reminder 1: send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only one day left to take advantage of this offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 3: From 15/11/2015 to 25/12/2015(Christmas time), create a coupon to obtain a gift on the order. Reminder 1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Surprise Gift&raquo; email. Reminder 2: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only a few days to benefit from the offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 4: For the cart &gt; &euro;900, the customer is professional Reminder 1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;More information about our catalog dedicated to professional&raquo; email. Reminder 2: Contact the customer by phone  My interest through Smart Cart Reminder module and the reminder rules: &rarr; &nbsp;I increase my sales &rarr; &nbsp;I control the cost of my marketing offers according to the cart &rarr; &nbsp;I approach as close as possible to the desire of my customers &rarr; &nbsp;I gain credibility by creating an intelligent and autonomous system which is no longer seen by my customers as an automatic emails or promotion distributor.  &nbsp;** MANY KINDS OF REMINDER &laquo;&nbsp;STANDARD&raquo; or &laquo;MANUAL&raquo; **&nbsp;Two kinds of reminders to adapt a little more to your reminder process:&laquo;Standard&raquo;: Sending an automatic email with a custom content of the cart to the customer.&laquo;&nbsp;Manual&raquo;: The module notifies you by email to communicate with the customer.You can even set the type of reminder that will suit your cart.  &nbsp;** AN INTERFACE DEDICATED TO &nbsp;&laquo;&nbsp;MANUAL &raquo; REMINDERS (PHONE) **&nbsp;In one page, the module includes all the information of your customers; and includes many features dedicated for your manual reminders.  My interest through&nbsp;my module &laquo;&nbsp;Smart Cart Reminder&nbsp;&raquo; and its page dedicated for manual reminders: &rarr; &nbsp;I don&rsquo;t lose anymore my customers information enabling me converting ( phone number, address, page visited, number of orders placed, current cart &hellip;) &rarr; I win in reactivity through the features present in this unique page: Sending a Pre-formatted email with the link of the complete order, creation of good (s) reduction (s) &rarr; I comment all my telephone conversations  &nbsp;** ADVANCED STATISTICS&nbsp;** &nbsp;The module provides a group of advanced reports easy-to-understand:The evolution of the generated sales according to cart remindersReports about the opened/clicked emailsCart reminder rule conversion reportsReports on employees manually remind customers. This report contains&nbsp;the number of orders made, the number of manual reminder processed for each employee. My interest through statistics is to improve me reminder system: &rarr; &nbsp;I improve my reminder emails to convert the maximum of cart &rarr; &nbsp;I improve my rules to build an autonomous system &rarr; &nbsp;I motivate my employees to increase my sales  &nbsp;** AN INTUITIVE AND EASY MODULE&nbsp;TO TAKE IN CHARGE ** &nbsp;&laquo;&nbsp;A quick start: Coming from a study conducted in the comb to a Committee of a dozen merchants, the module provides a clear and pleasant interface to use. Because we are committed to place the e-trader at the center of the process when we design our modules&raquo;  The module provides a range of features allowing you to act directly on the abandoned cart, you can manually raise without even that the countdown is finished, see explicit details of the choice of a rule for a cart...  My interest through its intuitive and transparent interface &nbsp;&nbsp; I spot in one glance: &rarr; The rules applied on the cart on each abandoned cart &rarr; The time left before the next reminder through the countdown &rarr; The list of reminders applied on the cart &rarr; If the reminder email was been seen and clicked &rarr; If the order was completed &rarr; &nbsp;...  &nbsp;** AN OPERATIONAL MODULE IN SOME CLICKS! ** &nbsp;1 Installation in 1 click and intuitive setting in 2 steps:1. I created my reminder emails, it&rsquo;s easy and fast! Several templates of emails delivered with the module, customize easily and quickly, select an example, edit the colors, edit the text, and here we go! 2- I create my cart reminder rules and I indicate for each rule the reminder emails to send.&nbsp;&nbsp;** A SUPPORT AT YOUR SERVICE&nbsp;**&laquo;Because your time is precious and that we want your full satisfaction!&nbsp;&raquo; &nbsp;You have particular difficulty for the integration, you have some questions. Our team will be glad to support you. We are very sensitive about the responsiveness and the quality of our responses. &nbsp; Source &laquo;&nbsp;addons.prestashop.com&nbsp;&raquo;:&nbsp; From 09/2013 to 08/2015&nbsp; Tickets received: 362 Handled: 362 Our overall service quality: 99.7% ** THEY BOUGHT THE MODULE AND YOU?**  20/08/2015 &laquo;Your module is terrific!!!&nbsp;&raquo;  15/08/2015 - 5/5 &laquo;Great module and great support!&nbsp;&raquo;  28/07/2015 - 5/5 Lots of options to help increase sales. Very friendly and responsive customer service. Highly recommended!  15/07/2015 - 5/5 Very good quality, congratulation.  &laquo;&nbsp;I tried the challenge and I am pleased, congratulations to the developers of this module.&nbsp; I like your system customizing email, this is top!&nbsp;&raquo; Cathy  &laquo;&nbsp;I&#39;m a merchant since 8 years ago, and I gave some ideas. In fact I wanted a new condition to treat new customers differently and according to my stock. A module that I don&rsquo;t leave no more! What flexibility! I paid the purchase in the first week. &raquo;&nbsp;Audrey&laquo;&nbsp;Don&rsquo;t hesitate to share with us your comments!&raquo;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.18]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pprod/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pbig/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19749]]></id><name><![CDATA[flashsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Premium Flash Sales]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Flash & Private Sales]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiply your shop sales using Flash Sales! Customisable and ideal for generating impulse buys, the Premium Flash Sales module increases your conversion rate and allows easy destocking]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/private-sales-flash-sales/19749-premium-flash-sale.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19749.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiply your shop sales using Flash Sales! Customisable and ideal for generating impulse buys, the Premium Flash Sales module increases your conversion rate and allows easy destocking. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your transformation rate by up to 59% thanks to flash sales!Boost your sales by giving your offers maximum visibilityLiquidate your stocks quickly and effectively to economise on storage costsLiven up your online shop easily and encourage your visitors to return to your store regularlyEncourage your indecisive customers to complete their purchases quickly because of the very limited duration of the offer and the countdown&nbsp; &nbsp; Expert tip: Send a newsletter to your customers to tell them about your flash sales using Official MailChimp (56% of businesses say they have a higher newsletter opening rate during flash sale periods) or inform your visitors when they reach your site thanks to a Pop Promo!  Comment posted on&nbsp;2015-11-05 09:51:48: &quot;Great! Works perfectly&quot; F. CASOLARI]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/672414-pprod/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/672414-pbig/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20242]]></id><name><![CDATA[bridgeconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Bridge Connector for Store Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fast & Mass Update]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bridge Connector allows you to connect Store Manager application to PrestaShop Cloud and perform advanced data update and input (import, export, mass edit, etc)]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/fast-mass-updates/20242-bridge-connector-for-store-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20242.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bridge Connector allows you to connect Store Manager application to PrestaShop Cloud and perform advanced data update and input (import, export, mass edit, etc). Should be used with Store Manager desktop application]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Merchants will get access to their&nbsp;PrestaShop Cloud database with the help of Store Manager and perform the following operations: - Work with categories and products on a single page - no reload required; - Change prices of multiple products at the same time (perfect for sales!); - Create product features and combinations in bulk; - Upload multiple images simultaneously (drag and drop directly onto the browser); - Quickly update your inventory, manage stock levels, warehouses, and stock movements; - Import products (including virtual), specific prices, multi-features, attribute values, customized fields, and combinations; - Import products from csv, txt, xml, xls/xslx (Excel), ods (OpenOffice). No file requirements - all missing data can be applied on the fly; - Import customers with passwords exported from another PrestaShop installation (requires additional assistance); - Create orders with a POS and process them in bulk (e.g. change status for multiple orders at once); - Use store diagnostics to fix missing or broken images; - Take advantage of powerful reporting features; - Manage multiple PrestaShop installations and shops with one back-office; - Work offline - all changes will be applied when you reconnect.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/691041-pprod/bridge-connector-for-store-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691041-pbig/bridge-connector-for-store-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20903]]></id><name><![CDATA[simplesitemap]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sitemap Simple (Multishop, Multilang & Blogs)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (natural Search Engine Optimization)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sitemap (mult-shop and multi-language), incorporating various blogging modules ! Get rid of an important point by combining SEO and simplicity thanks to this sitemap module ! It’s a plug and play modu]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/20903-sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20903.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sitemap (mult-shop and multi-language), incorporating various blogging modules ! Get rid of an important point by combining SEO and simplicity thanks to this sitemap module ! It’s a plug and play module ! Compliant with Google standards !  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[  Updated in real time with the latest published pages, fully customizable (you can block specific pages), it will load (for scheduled task) to prevent search engines at desired intervals. This module is multi-language and multishop: All your pages are indexed and listed in the languages ​​defined for each store/.  You can also include images or not, as you can turn off   Sitemap of or remove a link of it. It will also prevent robots (Google among others) the presence of it. It requires no special set-up action and adapts to any environment. Once installed, it's over, it works! No need to think about it! Easily customize the frequency of pages contained in the Sitemap. Automatic priority management is performed, calculated based on website updates.  It's necessary to stabilize a SEO / proper referencing in the ruthless world of the web, it will be an ideal and discreet companion, easy to implement. Simple, effective and very useful, this module is what all modules should do : a good job.  Sitemaps identified all sections of PrestaShop (products, categories, modules, CMS, rewrited URL's and suppliers). Implementation of Blogging modules within separates (for posts and categories) sitemaps too. Optimized SEO / SEO (Google / Bing / Yandex ) to make rapid progress your site to the top. Plug & Play : Once installed, it's ready ! Images included Separate Sitemaps for each shop and each containing selected languages ​​(multi-shop & multi-language) Support 24/7 to your every needs !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/716855-pprod/sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/716855-pbig/sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21318]]></id><name><![CDATA[magicredirect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Redirections URL (301 / Auto-fixing / Multishop / SEO)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[URL & Redirects]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Predicts and automatically fix missing pages ! Easily manage all your missing pages and your referrals (404, 301 etc) on your shop (Multi-shop & languages ready)]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/url-redirects/21318-redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21318.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Predicts and automatically fix missing pages ! Easily manage all your missing pages and your referrals (404, 301 etc) on your shop (Multi-shop & languages ready). Automaticly redirect disabled and deleted front office pages !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Magic Redirect saves you valuable time by doing for you most actions concerning your redirections (301) and your pages not found (404):Automaticly redirect any disabled/deleted object (products, manufacturers, suppliers, categories, cms pages and categories) to natural parent page.Be warned each new error, but is not intrusive.The module attempts to find internal links that could address these issues. You then have to activate them on the fly.Lead your customers more easily to the right pages.Create rules in the event of major changes on your shop.Lost pages are pre-filled to facilitate your work.Improve your SEO everyday. Google grants a bonus to websites regulating their 404!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/723026-pprod/redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/723026-pbig/redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22453]]></id><name><![CDATA[fastbay1]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[FastBay - eBay Marketplace synchronization]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[FASTBAY is the professional solution to synchronize your Prestashop store towards your Ebay account in few minutes ]]></description><author><![CDATA[Prestalia]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/marketplaces/22453-fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22453.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[FASTBAY is the professional solution to synchronize your Prestashop store towards your Ebay account in few minutes ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Over 1,250,000 Ebay Listings have been already created with FastBay.  EASY - A simplified configuration wizard will allow you to customize all settings without any problem in order to synchronize and manage products and orders. RELIABLE - Our module will assist you in every step of sync process and if you need assistance we guarantee a response within 48 hours. FLEXIBLE - FastBay guarantees many features that allows you to make a flexible site management that will suits all your needs. FAST - With our FastBay module your 'waiting times' will be reduced beyond belief ! Sync in a couple of minutes more than 5.000 products!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.4.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[269.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[209.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/748180-pprod/fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/748180-pbig/fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22666]]></id><name><![CDATA[onlinechat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Online Chat]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Support & Online Chat]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With the Online Chat module developed by PrestaShop, you can finally offer an online chat system on your shop to have discussions with your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/support-online-chat/22666-online-chat.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22666.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With the Online Chat module developed by PrestaShop, you can finally offer an online chat system on your shop to have discussions with your customers. This communication tool has become vital for e-commerce stores and allows you to create stronger relationships with your customers by guiding and advising them in their purchases in real time.   With this module that requires no subscription, improve your customer relations and your after-sales services, while increasing your conversion rate by up to 40%!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[No subscription needed; in just a few clicks you can set up your module and begin conversing with your online customers!&nbsp;You will find a simple, easy-to-use interface and a design that adapts perfectly to your site, in administration as for your store.&nbsp;With online conversations, you build a stronger, more human relationship with your customers and improve loyalty to your brand.&nbsp;You reduce the number of abandoned carts by answering your visitors&rsquo; questions directly.&nbsp;You save time in managing after-sales services by solving problems and requests live.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/752296-pprod/online-chat.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/752296-pbig/online-chat.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23517]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_easyplaces]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Places]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Registration & Ordering Process]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/registration-ordering-process/23517-easy-places.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23517.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature. Help your customers save time and reduce the number of customers who give up whilst creating an account from now on!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our Easy Places module helps you increase your transformation rate by simplifying the order creation process, by providing a feature that automatically enters the account creation or order addresses.  - "OK, but why do I need that ?" - When a new customer wants to place an order on your shop, you have to ask them for their delivery and invoicing address. Your customers find this compulsory and repetitive step annoying and frustrating. Some customers give up and go to another site where they know they have already entered all their information. What is more, shipping errors caused by customers entering their addresses incorrectly are not uncommon, entailing additional transport costs and decreased customer satisfaction owing to the delays caused by their parcels being sent out and returned again.  Easy Places is the ultimate solution for avoiding such problems! It allows you to offer your clients an elegant, high performance technical solution to make your account creation forms more pleasant to fill in.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766068-pprod/easy-places.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/766068-pbig/easy-places.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23671]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookproductad]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Ads + Pixel for THE Social Network]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of Facebook’s unmatched targeting and ROI with Facebook Product Ads and Remarketing]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/business-tech/23671-product-ads-pixel-for-the-social-network.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23671.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of Facebook’s unmatched targeting and ROI with Facebook Product Ads and Remarketing. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and customer repeat purchases on loyalty: Advertise your products on Facebook with Facebook Product Ads by exporting your product catalog to Facebook !  This is essentially the Facebook equivalent of Google Shopping / Merchant Center. But with unprecedented targeting options that Google can only dream of: age, sex, family situation, exact geographical location, interests, groups, pages and products liked, and all the impressive data Facebook has on each and everyone of your customers and prospects. An online marketer’s dream come true ! And the cost is also typically lower than Google’s, giving you a much better Return On Investment.  Just Like Google, Facebook has also implemented a Custom Audiences and Remarketing platform, allowing you to display ads to people who have previously visited your online shop or blog, and segmenting them in any way you see fit. Or you can also acquire new customers that are similar to your existing customers based on the information Facebook has on them and comparing it with information they have on your existing customers.  This is all done via the Facebook Pixel code, which also serves to track orders / conversions on your PrestaShop online store.  When you mix the Facebook Product Catalog with the Facebook Pixel, you get Dynamic Product Ads: the ability to retarget visitors from your site with the exact products they have viewed or with complementary ones. Dynamic Remarketing is extremely effective and offers a very high conversion rate and ROI.  This all-in-one module provides everything you need to get started right now with the world’s newest, most advanced and effective online advertising technology on the market. So, get on board TODAY so you don’t miss the boat !  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[26233]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestashop 1.7 user guide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop 1.7 User Guide (English version)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[User Guide]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[More than 300 pages and tips in English to guide you step by step! With the Official PrestaShop User Guide for 1]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/user-guide/26233-prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26233.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[More than 300 pages and tips in English to guide you step by step! With the Official PrestaShop User Guide for 1.7 in PDF format, find out how to easily configure your online store and use all its potential in order to increase your traffic, your sales and your turnover.  This 1.7 User Guide is also available in French &gt;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enjoy 100% of features available in your PrestaShop store!Save time by perfectly mastering your websiteThis user guide allows you to get to know all the functionalities available on PrestaShop 1.7. Soon you will be able to easily manage your PrestaShop store, and save time in your daily administration while optimizing your sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[14.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[16.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[13.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/824674-pprod/prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/824674-pbig/prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>